let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Is python case-sensistive?",
    answer: "yes",
    options: [
      "yes",
      "no",
      "machine dependant",
      "none of the mentioned"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which is an invalid variable?",
    answer: "1st_string",
    options: [
      "my_string_1",
      "1st_string",
      "foo",
      "_"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following cannot be a keyword?",
    answer: "in",
    options: [
      "__init__",
      "in",
      "it",
      "on"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which is the correct operator to calculate x to the power of y?",
    answer: "x**y",
    options: [
      "x^y",
      "x^^y",
      "x**y",
      "none of these"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "what is the answer to the expression 22%3",
    answer: "1",
    options: [
      "1",
      "7",
      "0",
      "5"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is the output of this expression: 3*1**3",
    answer: "3",
    options: [
      "9",
      "27",
      "1",
      "3"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is the output of print 0.1 + 0.2 == 0.3 ?",
    answer: "false",
    options: [
      "true",
      "false",
      "machine dependent",
      "error"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Result of cmp(3,1) is",
    answer: "1",
    options: [
      "1",
      "0",
      "true",
      "false"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What does 3 ^ 4 evaluate?",
    answer: "7",
    options: [
      "81",
      "12",
      "0.75",
      "7"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is the output when we execute list(“hello”)",
    answer: "[‘h’, ‘e’, ‘l’, ‘l’, ‘o’] ",
    options: [
      "[‘h’, ‘e’, ‘l’, ‘l’, ‘o’] ",
      "['hello']",
      "['llo']",
      "['olleh']"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Suppose list1 is [2, 33, 222, 14, 25], What is list1[-1]",
    answer: "25",
    options: [
      "Error",
      "None",
      "25",
      "2"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 12,
    question: "Which module in Python supports regular expressions?",
    answer: "re",
    options: [
      "re",
      "regex",
      "pyregex",
      "none of these"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 13,
    question: "What does the function re.match do?",
    answer: "matches a pattern at the start of the string",
    options: [
      "matches a pattern at the start of the string",
      "matches a pattern at any position in the string",
      "such a function does not exist",
      "none of the mentioned"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Which of the following statements create a dictionary?",
    answer: "All of the mentioned",
    options: [
      "d = {}",
      "d = {“john”:40, “peter”:45}",
      "d = {40:”john”, 45:”peter”}",
      "All of the mentioned"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 15,
    question: "What will be the output of the following Python code?  print('a B'.isalpha())",
    answer: "False",
    options: [
      "True",
      "False",
      "None",
      "Error"
    ]
  },

];

